## **Victor Brunell**

MS in Computer Science

Tallahassee, FL | (772) 214-0428 | vjb.tally@gmail.com | vbrunell.github.io | github.com/vbrunell

#### **ABOUT**

I graduated from Florida State University with an MS in Computer Science in the Summer 2017 Semester. My thesis research involved code optimization using an optimizing compiler to improve instruction-level parallelism in superscalar processors. My research interests include compilers, computer architecture, programming language design, data science, mobile programming, and machine learning.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Florida State University MS in Computer Science

2015 – 2017 **GPA:** 4.0

**Thesis:** Dependency Collapsing in Instruction-Level Parallel Architectures

**Selected Coursework:** Compiler Construction, Advanced Topics in Compilation, Computer Architecture, Artificial Intelligence, Data and Computer Communications, Mobile Programming, Computer and Network Administration, Theory of Automata and Formal Languages

Florida State University BA in Asian Studies / Business

2000 - 2006

#### **SKILLS**

Languages: C, C++, Java, Python, SQL, MIPS, SPARC Web/Mobile: HTML, CSS, Android, Android Studio Networks: Windows Server, Active Directory

Cloud: VMWare, vSphere, Google Cloud Platform

Operating Systems: Unix, Linux, Android, Windows

Graphical: Adobe Photoshop, Inkscape, Macromedia Suite Other: Git, \*nix Scripting, Flex/Bison, Bash, Vim, LaTeX

Natural Languages: Japanese (JLPT 2)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Research/Teaching Assistant, Florida State University

Tallahassee, FL 2015 – Present

- Computer architecture and optimizing compiler research.
- > Developing new compiler optimizations, ALU designs, and architecture simulator.
- Collaborating with research teams across three universities.
- ➤ Teaching courses in C++, computer architecture and design, and algorithm analysis.
- Working with a team of educators and computer scientists to develop curricula for computer science education in Florida's middle schools as part of the CSIMMS project.

## IT/Business Consultant, Coastal Water Systems

Tallahassee, FL 2012 – Present

- > IT troubleshooting; Network and website development and administration.
- Modernizing and managing the company's business systems.

#### ALT Coordinator / English Teacher, Tokushima Board of Education

Tokushima, Japan

2006 - 2011

- Coordinator for 75 foreign English teachers (ALTs).
- > Teaching English to Japanese senior high school students.
- Organizing and moderating various workshops and seminars.
- Administering websites serving the English-teaching community.
- > Japanese-English translation and interpretation.

#### Network Admin / Junior Software Developer, Ben Johnson Associates

Tallahassee, FL

2004 - 2005

- Part of a team developing a specialized search engine.
- Database development and data parsing.
- Set up and managed the project server.
- Full stack development.

## Web Developer, Cennexus

Tallahassee, FL

2002 - 2003

- Designed and developed websites for local businesses and organizations.
- Provided IT support to local businesses.